<!DOCTYPE balsa SYSTEM "http://balsa.intrbiz.net/balsa.dtd">
<?RenderLibrary com.intrbiz.balsa?>
<!-- The index view -->
<fragment xmlns="com.intrbiz.balsa" title="Welcome">
    <div class="recent_posts">
        <h3>Recent Posts</h3>
        <ul>
            <data-set var="post" value="#{posts}">
                <li><a href="#{'post/' + post.name}">#{post.title}</a></li>
            </data-set>
        </ul>
    </div>
    <div class="post">
        <h2>Welcome to Intrbiz, IT consultancy for Open Source Software</h2>
        <p>
            We are a small independent IT consultancy specialising in a range of Open Source software.  We've been working with Open Source software for over a decade and have extensive experience of:
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>PostgreSQL</li>
            <li>Linux</li>
            <li>Apache</li>
            <li>Nagios</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            Our primary expertese is around PostgreSQL, having utilised and deployed PostgreSQL for many different applications.  Including using PL/Proxy to build heavily sharded PostgreSQL database clusters, targeted at write and read scaling.  We've routinely worked with multi-terrabyte databases with demanding and complex ETL setups.  We have extensive experience of devloping applications with PostgreSQL, performance tuning and day to day database administration.
        </p>
        <p>
            We are also the lead developers of <a href="https://bergamot-monitoring.org/">Bergamot Monitoring</a> a distributed infrastructure monitoring solution with an easy migration path from Nagios.
        </p>
        <p>
            Bergamot Monitoring provides a scalable monitoring solution capable of handling the complexities of modern world, where infrastructure can be on-premise and/or in the cloud.  Bergamot Monitoring provides a modern, real time user interface, with zero downtime configuration changes.  The distributed nature of Bergamot Monitoring create a highly robust solution, requiring minimal downtime and a scalable platform which can grow as you do.
        </p>
    </div>
</fragment>
